<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[IPL 2024 - Latest News & Live Updates]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[IPL 2024 - Latest News & Live Updates]]></description>
        <link>https://g11prediction.com/</link>
        <image>
            <url>https://g11prediction.com/image/G11.png</url>
            <title>IPL 2024 - Latest News &amp; Live Updates</title>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/</link>
        </image>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 07:45:35 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://g11prediction.com/Rss/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023RSS-feed.xml/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 07:45:35 GMT</pubDate>
        <language><![CDATA[en]]></language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Muttiah Mualitharan Wants Rohit To Play Another World Cup, And Said "he'll play another World cup"]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Renowned Sri Lankan off-spinner, Muttiah Muralitharan, has expressed robust support for Rohit Sharma&#39;s inclusion in the approaching 2024 T20 World Cup, slated to spread in the dynamic cricketing places of the West Indies and the United States. Despite speculation surrounding Rohit&#39;s destiny in T20 Internationals following India&#39;s unfulfilled quest for the 2023 World Cup, the 51-year-vintage cricketing legend emphasizes the importance of Rohit Sharma&#39;s participation in the approaching match.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Muttiah-Mualitharan Wants Rohit To Play Another World Cup- And Said -he-ll play another World cup-/850</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Muttiah-Mualitharan Wants Rohit To Play Another World Cup- And Said -he-ll play another World cup-/850</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 09:46:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Returned to village after defeat in World Cup final]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Returned to village after defeat in World Cup final; Shami said &ndash; Australian player insulted the trophy

Indian team&#39;s fast bowler Mohammed Shami reached Sahaspur in his village Amroha. Where he hugged his mother first.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Returned-to village after defeat in World Cup final/849</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Returned-to village after defeat in World Cup final/849</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 04:13:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[India's biggest run chase against Australia in T-20]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[India&#39;s biggest run chase against Australia in T-20: Surya is the Indian captain who scored the most runs in the first match.
India achieved a thrilling 2-wicket victory over Australia in the first match of the T-20 series. With this victory, the team has taken a 1-0 lead in the 5-match series. The second match of the series will be played on 26 November in Thiruvananthapuram.

On Thursday in Visakhapatnam, Indian batsmen achieved the target of 209 runs by losing 8 wickets in the last ball of the 20th over. Captain Suryakumar Yadav played an inning of 80 runs on 42 balls, while Ishan Kishan scored 58 runs. Many interesting facts and records were seen during this match.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-s-biggest run chase against Australia in T-20/848</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-s-biggest run chase against Australia in T-20/848</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 03:49:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ICC ODI Rankings, Kohli moved from fourth to third position: Three Indians in top-4]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[ICC ODI Rankings, Kohli moved from fourth to third position: Three Indians in top-4, Gill remains on top, Siraj slipped one place in bowling.

Virat Kohli has 791 rating points in the latest ODI rankings.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ICC-ODI Rankings- Kohli moved from fourth to third position- Three Indians in top-4/847</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ICC-ODI Rankings- Kohli moved from fourth to third position- Three Indians in top-4/847</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 04:23:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rohit Sharma will not play T-20 International: Report claims conversation with Chief Selector Agarka]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Rohit Sharma will not play T-20 International: Report claims conversation with Chief Selector Agarkar; Will not play after T-20 World Cup

Indian Captain Rohit Sharma will no longer play in T-20 International. It has been claimed in Media Buddh that Rohit had already discussed this matter with Chief Selector Ajit Agarkar even before the World Cup.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Rohit-Sharma will not play T-20 International- Report claims conversation with Chief Selector Agarka/846</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Rohit-Sharma will not play T-20 International- Report claims conversation with Chief Selector Agarka/846</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 04:13:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Will Rohit-Virat not play in the World Cup now, Sharma will be 40, Kohli 39 by 2027]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Will Rohit-Virat not play in the World Cup now?; Sharma will be 40, Kohli 39 by 2027

For Indian fans, the dream of winning the Cricket World Cup still remains a dream. After 12 years, the team made it to the finals but Australia made the wait longer to win the trophy. Captain Rohit Sharma and experienced Virat Kohli tried their best but could not make the team champion.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Will-Rohit-Virat not play in the World Cup now- Sharma will be 40- Kohli 39 by 2027/845</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Will-Rohit-Virat not play in the World Cup now- Sharma will be 40- Kohli 39 by 2027/845</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 04:48:27 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[T20 team announced against Australia: Surya captain, Samson no chance; 3 players of World Cup squad]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[T20 team announced against Australia: Surya captain, Samson no chance; 3 players of World Cup squad included

The Indian team has been announced for the 5 T-20 match series against Australia. Suryakumar Yadav has been made the captain of this young team, while experienced wicketkeeper-batsman Sanju Samson has not got a chance.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/T20-team announced against Australia- Surya captain- Samson no chance- 3 players of World Cup squad/844</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/T20-team announced against Australia- Surya captain- Samson no chance- 3 players of World Cup squad/844</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 04:04:31 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ICC announced the World Cup Team of the Tournament: 6 Indians in the list of 12 players]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[ICC announced the World Cup Team of the Tournament: 6 Indians in the list of 12 players, Rohit captain; 2 Australian players included

The International Cricket Council (ICC) has announced the &#39;Team of the Tournament&#39; for the World Cup 2023. The captain of this team is Rohit Sharma, who made his team win 10 consecutive matches in this tournament. Maximum 6 Indian players are included in this list.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ICC-announced the World Cup Team of the Tournament- 6 Indians in the list of 12 players/843</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ICC-announced the World Cup Team of the Tournament- 6 Indians in the list of 12 players/843</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 12:44:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PM Modi hugged Shami in the dressing room and encouraged the players after the defeat]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[PM Modi hugged Shami in the dressing room and encouraged the players after the defeat; Jadeja-Shami posted photos

The final match of the World Cup 2023 was played between India and Australia on Sunday. In this match, Australia defeated India by six wickets and became world champion for the sixth time. After the defeat in the final, Prime Minister Narendra Modi reached the dressing room of Team India. There he was seen encouraging the players. During this he also hugged Shami. Team&#39;s fast bowler Mohammed Shami and star all-rounder Ravindra Jadeja have shared the photo of this meeting.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/PM-Modi hugged Shami in the dressing room and encouraged the players after the defeat/842</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/PM-Modi hugged Shami in the dressing room and encouraged the players after the defeat/842</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 12:32:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fear of defeat defeated India again: Played 10 ICC tournaments since 2013, lost final-semi-final]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Fear of defeat defeated India again: Played 10 ICC tournaments since 2013, lost final-semi-final for the 9th time
Team India once again lost the chance to win the ICC trophy. Australia defeated India by 7 wickets in the World Cup final played at Narendra Modi Stadium in Ahmedabad on Sunday.

This is the 9th time since 2013 that the Indian team has lost the chance to win the title by losing the semi-final or final match.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Fear-of defeat defeated India again- Played 10 ICC tournaments since 2013- lost final-semi-final/841</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Fear-of defeat defeated India again- Played 10 ICC tournaments since 2013- lost final-semi-final/841</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 16:13:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Australia won the ODI World Cup for the sixth time: Beat India by 6 wickets in the final]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Australia won the ODI World Cup for the sixth time: Beat India by 6 wickets in the final, Travis Head scored 137 runs on 120 balls.
Team India has lost only the final match in this World Cup. Before this, the team won 10 consecutive matches. Australian captain Pat Cummins won the toss and decided to bowl first.
India has suffered a crushing defeat by 6 wickets in the final of the World Cup 2023. On Sunday, Australia won the ODI World Cup title for the sixth time. This defeat reminded Indian fans of the 2003 World Cup final. 20 years ago the Kangaroos beat us by 125 runs in Johannesburg.

After losing the toss and batting first, Team India was all out for 240 runs at the Narendra Modi Stadium in Ahmedabad. Australian batsmen achieved the target of 241 runs by losing 4 wickets in 43 overs. Travis Head scored a century of 137 runs, while Marnus Labuschagne scored an unbeaten 58 runs. Earlier, Mitchell Starc took 3 wickets, while captain Pat Cummins and Josh Hazlewood got 2 wickets each.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Australia-won the ODI World Cup for the sixth time- Beat India by 6 wickets in the final/840</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Australia-won the ODI World Cup for the sixth time- Beat India by 6 wickets in the final/840</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 19 Nov 2023 16:05:12 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pritam-Amit Mishra will perform at the World Cup 2023 closing ceremony.  The closing ceremony of the]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Pritam-Amit Mishra will perform at the World Cup 2023 closing ceremony.

The closing ceremony of the ODI World Cup 2023 will take place on Sunday itself, the day of the final match. The ceremony programs will be held in four stages. Which will take place in the pre-match, drinks break of the first innings, innings break and drinks break of the second innings. Many artists including Bollywood composer-singer Pritam, Amit Mishra will perform in it.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Pritam-Amit-Mishra will perform at the World Cup 2023 closing ceremony-  The closing ceremony of the/839</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Pritam-Amit-Mishra will perform at the World Cup 2023 closing ceremony-  The closing ceremony of the/839</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 16:21:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Indian Team Wants To Win World Cup 2023 For Rahul Dravid]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Indian Cricket Team Captain Rohit Sharma dedicated the team&#39;s success to the head coach Rahul Dravid for his approach of giving every player individual liberty to play their own game. In every challenging moment, David gives great support to every player.&nbsp;]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Indian-Team Wants To Win World Cup 2023 For Rahul Dravid/838</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Indian-Team Wants To Win World Cup 2023 For Rahul Dravid/838</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 15:27:36 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ICC invites all champion captains to the World Cup final]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[ICC invites all champion captains to the World Cup final

The International Cricket Council (ICC) has invited all the previous World Cup champion captains (from 1975 to 2019) for the ODI World Cup 2023 final match. Imran Khan, who made neighboring country Pakistan win the World Cup in 1992, is in jail. In such a situation, it is impossible for him to come. Now it remains to be seen whether captain Arjun Ranatunga, who made Sri Lanka the champion in 1996, will come or not.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ICC-invites all champion captains to the World Cup final/837</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ICC-invites all champion captains to the World Cup final/837</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 15:07:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Australia in the World Cup final for the 8th time: match against India on 19 November]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Australia in the World Cup final for the 8th time: match against India on 19 November

Australia defeated South Africa by 3 wickets in the second semi-final played at Eden Gardens Ground in Kolkata. The Australian team has reached the final of this tournament for the 8th time. At the same time, South Africa once again proved to be a chokers team in a big tournament. This is the fifth time that the African team has lost in the semi-finals of the ODI World Cup.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Australia-in the World Cup final for the 8th time- match against India on 19 November/836</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Australia-in the World Cup final for the 8th time- match against India on 19 November/836</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 06:14:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SA Vs AUS Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction SA Vs AUS World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[SA Vs AUS Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction SA Vs AUS World Cup 2023

Welcome to the pinnacle of cricketing excitement as the ICC World Cup 2023 reaches its knockout stage. Brace yourselves for an epic showdown in Semi Final 2, where cricketing powerhouses Australia and South Africa will clash on the revered grounds of Eden Gardens on 16th November 2023.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/SA-Vs AUS Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction SA Vs AUS World Cup 2023/835</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/SA-Vs AUS Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction SA Vs AUS World Cup 2023/835</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 05:09:49 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[World Cup 2023: Won semi-final after 12 years, Virat's first century in knockout]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[World Cup 2023: Won semi-final after 12 years, Virat&#39;s first century in knockout

10th consecutive win for the first time in the World Cup. New Zealand defeated in the semi-finals for the first time. Win after two consecutive defeats in the semis.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/World-Cup 2023- Won semi-final after 12 years- Virat-s first century in knockout/834</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/World-Cup 2023- Won semi-final after 12 years- Virat-s first century in knockout/834</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 04:52:24 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Virat has the most centuries in ODI cricket; Broke Sachin's record by scoring 50th century]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Virat has the most centuries in ODI cricket; Broke Sachin&#39;s record by scoring 50th century

Virat Kohli played an inning of 117 runs off 113 balls. He scored the 50th century of his ODI career. He became the batsman with the most centuries in ODIs. Virat broke Sachin Tendulkar&#39;s record of 49 centuries. On the other hand, Shreyas Iyer scored 105 runs on 70 balls. Iyer scored his second consecutive century in the World Cup. Shubman Gill scored 80 runs on 66 balls and captain Rohit Sharma scored 47 runs on 29 balls. Tim Southee took 2 wickets for New Zealand.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Virat-has the most centuries in ODI cricket- Broke Sachin-s record by scoring 50th century/833</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Virat-has the most centuries in ODI cricket- Broke Sachin-s record by scoring 50th century/833</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 12:34:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[World Cup 2023 Semi-Final-1 today: India and New Zealand will face each other in the second consecut]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[World Cup 2023 Semi-Final-1 today: India and New Zealand will face each other in the second consecutive knockout

The first semi-final match of ODI World Cup 2023 will be held today i.e. on 15th November in Mumbai. The match will be played between table-topper India and 2019 runner-up New Zealand. The match will start at 2:00 pm at Wankhede Stadium, with the toss taking place at 1:30 pm.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/World-Cup 2023 Semi-Final-1 today- India and New Zealand will face each other in the second consecut/832</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/World-Cup 2023 Semi-Final-1 today- India and New Zealand will face each other in the second consecut/832</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 04:53:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IND Vs NZ Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction IND Vs NZ World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[IND Vs NZ Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction IND Vs NZ World Cup 2023

The first Semi-Final game of the ICC World Cup 2023 will see the clash between India and New Zealand on the 15th of November at the Wankhede Stadium, Mumbai. Both teams played 9 games in the tournament&rsquo;s league stage. India won all of their 9 games in the tournament, and ended the league stage at the top of the points table, with 18 points to their tally and a net run rate of +2.570. They won their last game against the Netherlands by 160 runs.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/IND-Vs NZ Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction IND Vs NZ World Cup 2023/831</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/IND-Vs NZ Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction IND Vs NZ World Cup 2023/831</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 09:42:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How can India beat New Zealand: Rachin, Boult and Santner are big threats]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[How can India beat New Zealand: Rachin, Boult and Santner are big threats

The first semi-final of the ODI World Cup 2023 between India and New Zealand will be played on Wednesday, November 15. In this World Cup, India has defeated New Zealand in the league match, but facing the Kiwi team at the Wankhede Stadium in Mumbai will be a completely different challenge.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/How-can India beat New Zealand- Rachin- Boult and Santner are big threats/830</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/How-can India beat New Zealand- Rachin- Boult and Santner are big threats/830</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 05:29:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rahul is the Indian who scored the fastest century in the World Cup]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Rahul is the Indian who scored the fastest century in the World Cup: Rohit scored the most sixes, Kohli scored 50+ for the 7th time.

India&#39;s winning campaign continues in the World Cup 2023. The team defeated Netherlands by 160 runs in the last league match on Sunday. The Indian team has achieved its ninth consecutive win in this tournament. For the first time in World Cup history, Team India has won nine consecutive matches in a season.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Rahul-is the Indian who scored the fastest century in the World Cup/829</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Rahul-is the Indian who scored the fastest century in the World Cup/829</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 04:58:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[India's 9th consecutive win in the World Cup: Beat Netherlands by 160 runs, Iyer-Rahul's centuries]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[India&#39;s 9th consecutive win in the World Cup: Beat Netherlands by 160 runs, Iyer-Rahul&#39;s centuries

India continues its winning campaign in the World Cup 2023. The team defeated Netherlands by 160 runs in the last league match. This is India&#39;s ninth consecutive victory in the World Cup. For the first time, Team India has won nine consecutive matches in a World Cup.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-s-9th consecutive win in the World Cup- Beat Netherlands by 160 runs- Iyer-Rahul-s centuries/828</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-s-9th consecutive win in the World Cup- Beat Netherlands by 160 runs- Iyer-Rahul-s centuries/828</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 04:32:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[What will happen if the semi-finals are washed out in the rain]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[What will happen if the semi-finals are washed out in the rain: The match will be held on the reserve day

The first semi-final of the World Cup is to be held between India and New Zealand on 15 November in Mumbai.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/What-will happen if the semi-finals are washed out in the rain/827</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/What-will happen if the semi-finals are washed out in the rain/827</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 04:16:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Last match of World Cup league stage India vs Netherlands: Dutch team eyes Champions Trophy]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Last match of World Cup league stage India vs Netherlands: Dutch team eyes Champions Trophy

India will face Netherlands in the ODI World Cup 2023 today on the occasion of Diwali. The match will start at 2:00 PM at M Chinnaswamy Stadium, Bengaluru, the toss will take place at 1:30 PM. Both teams will play the 45th and last match of the league stage.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Last-match of World Cup league stage India vs Netherlands- Dutch team eyes Champions Trophy/826</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Last-match of World Cup league stage India vs Netherlands- Dutch team eyes Champions Trophy/826</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 03:49:20 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IND Vs NED Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction IND Vs NED World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[IND Vs NED Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction IND Vs NED World Cup 2023

India will compete against the Netherlands in the match 45th of the ODI World Cup 2023 at the M Chinnaswamy Stadium in Bengaluru. With eight straight wins in the CWC 2023, the Men in Blue have been the most dominant team of the flagship tournament, while the Dutch have managed to secure only a couple of victories thus far. India have already defeated the Netherlands twice in the ODI World Cup history, a trend which is expected to continue as per their current form on November 12.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/IND-Vs NED Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction IND Vs NED World Cup 2023/825</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/IND-Vs NED Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction IND Vs NED World Cup 2023/825</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 05:49:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Today first match AUS vs BAN, Today Match Prediction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Today first match AUS vs BAN,&nbsp;Today Match Prediction

Today in the ODI World Cup 2023, the match is being played between Australia and Bangladesh. The match will take place at the MCA Stadium in Pune from 10:30 am. Australia won the toss and decided to field.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Today-first match AUS vs BAN-Today Match Prediction/824</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Today-first match AUS vs BAN-Today Match Prediction/824</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 05:22:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ENG Vs PAK Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction ENG Vs PAK World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[ENG Vs PAK Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction ENG Vs PAK World Cup 2023

England will compete against Pakistan in the 44th match of the ODI World Cup 2023 at the Eden Gardens in Kolkata. The English registered their second win of the CWC 2023 to keep their hopes for a spot in the ICC Champions Trophy 2025 alive, while the Men in Green got the better of New Zealand on DLS to stay in the hunt for the semi-final. Although Pakistan got the better of England in the last edition of the quadrennial spectacle, they haven&rsquo;t had the best of times in the bilaterals afterward, which could mean a really competitive contest between these two countries on November 11.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ENG-Vs PAK Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction ENG Vs PAK World Cup 2023/823</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ENG-Vs PAK Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction ENG Vs PAK World Cup 2023/823</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 07:35:47 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[India Will be able to defeat New Zealand in the semi-finals?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[India Will be able to defeat New Zealand in the semi-finals? There were three clashes in the knockout of ICC tournament; New Zealand won every time.

New Zealand has almost confirmed its place in the ODI World Cup semi-finals with a big win over Sri Lanka. The team defeated Sri Lanka by 5 wickets in 23.2 overs on Thursday and made its run rate much higher than Pakistan and Afghanistan.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-Will be able to defeat New Zealand in the semi-finals-/822</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-Will be able to defeat New Zealand in the semi-finals-/822</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 06:59:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[France Cricket Has Been Accused Of Fraud And Corruption]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[France Cricket has been accused of allegations of fraud and corruption, including a potential investigation by The International Cricket Council (ICC). The ICC Team said to the media, &quot;We&#39;re looking into it,&quot; in response to a report in the French press, which asserted that France Cricket has significantly exaggerated claims about the conduct of matches. The report alleges that France Cricket has been involved in the fabrication of matches and has submitted falsified information to the ICC.&quot;]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/France-Cricket Has Been Accused Of Fraud And Corruption/821</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/France-Cricket Has Been Accused Of Fraud And Corruption/821</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2023 06:53:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA['Do-or-die' stage of World Cup begins: New Zealand-Sri Lanka clash today, if Kiwis win, semi-finals]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[&#39;Do-or-die&#39; stage of World Cup begins: New Zealand-Sri Lanka clash today, if Kiwis win, semi-finals almost certain]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/-Do-or-die-stage of World Cup begins- New Zealand-Sri Lanka clash today- if Kiwis win- semi-finals/820</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/-Do-or-die-stage of World Cup begins- New Zealand-Sri Lanka clash today- if Kiwis win- semi-finals/820</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 04:54:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Australia won with Maxwell's double century: Afghanistan lost despite losing 7 wickets for 91 runs]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Australia won with Maxwell&#39;s double century: Afghanistan lost despite losing 7 wickets for 91 runs.

During the Afghanistan and Australia match at Wankhede, cricket fans saw such courage of a cricketer, which cannot be easily trusted. Glenn Maxwell, who played an unbeaten inning of 201 runs.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Australia-won with Maxwell-s double century- Afghanistan lost despite losing 7 wickets for 91 runs/819</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Australia-won with Maxwell-s double century- Afghanistan lost despite losing 7 wickets for 91 runs/819</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 05:18:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ENG Vs NED: Netherlands looking for first ODI win against England, battle for top-8 continues]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[ENG Vs NED: Netherlands looking for first ODI win against England, battle for top-8 continues

Today the match will be played between Netherlands and England in the ODI World Cup. The match will be held at MCA Stadium in Pune from 2 pm. The toss will take place at 1:30 pm.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ENG-Vs NED- Netherlands looking for first ODI win against England- battle for top-8 continues/818</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ENG-Vs NED- Netherlands looking for first ODI win against England- battle for top-8 continues/818</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 05:15:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ENG vs NED Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction ENG vs NED World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[ENG vs NED Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction ENG vs NED World Cup 2023]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ENG-vs NED Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction ENG vs NED World Cup 2023/817</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ENG-vs NED Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction ENG vs NED World Cup 2023/817</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 04:19:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Time out controversy: Mathews said - Shakib and Bangladesh's action is very shameful]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Time out controversy: Mathews said - Shakib and Bangladesh&#39;s action is very shameful; Shakib- Whatever I did was right

Angelo Mathews returned to the pavilion without facing any ball in the match.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Time-out controversy- Mathews said - Shakib and Bangladesh-s action is very shameful/816</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Time-out controversy- Mathews said - Shakib and Bangladesh-s action is very shameful/816</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 04:01:30 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SL vs BAN: Sri Lanka has last chance for semi-final qualification, have not lost to Bangladesh]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[SL vs BAN: Sri Lanka has last chance for semi-final qualification, have not lost to Bangladesh

The 38th match of the ODI World Cup 2023 will be played today on 6th November between Sri Lanka and Bangladesh at the Arun Jaitley Stadium in Delhi. The match will start at 2:00 pm. The toss will take place half an hour before the match at 1:30 pm.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/SL-vs BAN- Sri Lanka has last chance for semi-final qualification- have not lost to Bangladesh/815</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/SL-vs BAN- Sri Lanka has last chance for semi-final qualification- have not lost to Bangladesh/815</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 07:09:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AUS vs AFG Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction AUS vs AFG World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[AUS vs AFG Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction AUS vs AFG World Cup 2023

The action will continue in the ongoing World Cup as Australia, the most successful team in ICC events, are about to face Afghanistan in the 39th game. This highly anticipated match will take place at the Wankhede Stadium, Mumbai, on Tunesday, November 7th, at 02:00 pm IST. Currently, Australia has won 5 out of 7 matches and are in 3rd place on the points table with 10 points. On the other hand, Afghanistan are entering this game after a 7 wickets win against Netherlands in 34th game at the Ekana stadium and kept hope alive to make the playoffs this year. They have played 7 matches in this campaign and are at the 6th of the points table with 8 points.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/AUS-vs AFG Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction AUS vs AFG World Cup 2023/814</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/AUS-vs AFG Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction AUS vs AFG World Cup 2023/814</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 04:02:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BAN vs SL Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction BAN vs SL World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[BAN vs SL Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction BAN vs SL World Cup 2023

Bangladesh cricket team will face Sri Lanka in the 38th contest of the ICC Cricket World Cup 2023. This high-stakes encounter is scheduled for 6th November 2023 at 2.00 PM (Indian Time) and will take place at the Arun Jaitley Stadium, Delhi.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/BAN-vs SL Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction BAN vs SL World Cup 2023/813</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/BAN-vs SL Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction BAN vs SL World Cup 2023/813</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 17:04:46 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[India's eighth consecutive victory in the World Cup after 20 years: South Africa's biggest defeat]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[India&#39;s eighth consecutive victory in the World Cup after 20 years: South Africa&#39;s biggest defeat

India has registered its eighth consecutive win in the ODI World Cup by defeating South Africa by 243 runs in a one-sided match. With this, India also decided to finish at number-1 position in the points table. That means India will face the fourth ranked team in the semi-finals.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-s-eighth consecutive victory in the World Cup after 20 years- South Africa-s biggest defeat/812</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-s-eighth consecutive victory in the World Cup after 20 years- South Africa-s biggest defeat/812</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 05 Nov 2023 16:58:15 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pakistan won with Fakhar Zaman's century]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Pakistan won with Fakhar Zaman&#39;s century: New Zealand was defeated by 21 runs under DLS method, hopes of semi-finals remain intact.

Pakistan has defeated New Zealand by 21 runs under the Duckworth-Lewis method in the rain-affected World Cup match. With this victory on Saturday, Pakistan team has come to 5th position in the points table and remains in the race for the semi-finals. Fakhar Zaman scored unbeaten 126 runs on 81 balls and captain Babar Azam scored unbeaten 66 runs on 63 balls.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Pakistan-won with Fakhar Zaman-s century/811</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Pakistan-won with Fakhar Zaman-s century/811</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 17:54:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Defending champion England out of World Cup: Australia defeated by 33 runs]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Defending champion England out of World Cup: Australia defeated by 33 runs]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Defending-champion England out of World Cup- Australia defeated by 33 runs/810</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Defending-champion England out of World Cup- Australia defeated by 33 runs/810</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 17:43:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ENG vs AUS Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction ENG vs AUS World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[ENG vs AUS Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction ENG vs AUS World Cup 2023

England will compete against Australia in the match 36th of the ODI World Cup 2023 at the Narendra Modi Stadium in Ahmedabad. The English have suffered five losses in their six matches, while the Aussies have won four matches on the spin to keep themselves well within reach of the semi-final spot in the flagship tournament. With such stark difference in their current results, Australia is the likeliest to achieve the win against England, but they will have to bring their A-game at all times on November 4.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ENG-vs AUS Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction ENG vs AUS World Cup 2023/809</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ENG-vs AUS Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction ENG vs AUS World Cup 2023/809</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 08:03:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NZ Vs PAK Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction NZ Vs PAK World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[NZ Vs PAK Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction NZ Vs PAK World Cup 2023

New Zealand will take on Pakistan in the 35th match of the ODI World Cup 2023 at the M Chinnaswamy Stadium in Bengaluru. The Blackcaps have lost three matches in a row, which has put their hopes for qualification in the semi-final of the quadrennial spectacle in jeopardy, while the Men in Green registered a thumping win against Bangladesh to keep their hopes alive. The contrasting form for both the teams puts Pakistan in the box seat to achieve a positive result in their upcoming ODI World Cup 2023 fixture, but New Zealand are not going to go down without a fight.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/NZ-Vs PAK Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction NZ Vs PAK World Cup 2023/808</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/NZ-Vs PAK Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction NZ Vs PAK World Cup 2023/808</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 05:38:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AFG vs NED: Netherlands-Afghanistan will face each other for the first time in the World Cup]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[AFG vs NED: Netherlands-Afghanistan will face each other for the first time in the World Cup

Afghanistan will face the Netherlands in the 34th match of the ODI World Cup 2023 today on 3rd November. The match will be played at Bharat Ratna Shri Atal Bihari Vajpayee Ekana Cricket Stadium, Lucknow from 2 pm. The toss will take place half an hour before the match at 1:30 p.m. Netherlands and Afghanistan will face each other for the first time in the World Cup.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/AFG-vs NED- Netherlands-Afghanistan will face each other for the first time in the World Cup/807</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/AFG-vs NED- Netherlands-Afghanistan will face each other for the first time in the World Cup/807</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 03 Nov 2023 05:19:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NED Vs AFG Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction NED Vs AFG World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[NED Vs AFG Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction NED Vs AFG World Cup 2023

In the 34th match of the ODI World Cup 2023, Netherlands will go head-to-head against Afghanistan at the Ekana Cricket Stadium in Lucknow. This match is going to be very important for both teams. Because the path to the semi-finals is still open for both teams.&nbsp; If both the teams perform well in the remaining matches then they can be successful in making their place in the top four.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/NED-Vs AFG Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction NED Vs AFG World Cup 2023/806</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/NED-Vs AFG Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction NED Vs AFG World Cup 2023/806</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 06:12:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IND vs SL: India will try to secure a place in the semi-finals, victory is necessary for Sri Lanka]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[IND vs SL: India will try to secure a place in the semi-finals, victory is necessary for Sri Lanka

Today, the two-time world champion Indian team will face Sri Lanka in the ODI World Cup. The match will be played at Wankhede Stadium in Mumbai from 2 pm. The toss will take place half an hour before the match at 1:30 p.m.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/IND-vs SL- India will try to secure a place in the semi-finals- victory is necessary for Sri Lanka/805</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/IND-vs SL- India will try to secure a place in the semi-finals- victory is necessary for Sri Lanka/805</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2023 05:25:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IND vs SL Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction IND vs SL World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[IND vs SL Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction IND vs SL World Cup 2023

India (IND) will lock horns against the Sri Lanka (SL) on Thursday (Nov 2) at the Wankhede Stadium, Mumbai in the 33rd game of the WC 2023. India is the only team in this competition that has not lost a single match yet, and is at the first position in the points table, with 12 points. If we talk about Sri Lanka, it is at sixth place in the points table after winning only two out of 6 matches.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/IND-vs SL Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction IND vs SL World Cup 2023/804</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/IND-vs SL Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction IND vs SL World Cup 2023/804</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 05:17:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NZ vs SA match today: In 2015, New Zealand broke its dream of playing the final]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[NZ vs SA match today: In 2015, New Zealand broke its dream of playing the final.

Current runner-up New Zealand will face South Africa today in the 32nd match of the ODI World Cup 2023. The match will be played at the Maharashtra Cricket Association Stadium (MCA), Pune from 2:00 pm onwards. The toss will take place at 1:30 pm before the match.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/NZ-vs SA match today- In 2015- New Zealand broke its dream of playing the final/803</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/NZ-vs SA match today- In 2015- New Zealand broke its dream of playing the final/803</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2023 05:13:47 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PAK vs BAN match today: Pakistan must win to maintain hopes of semi-finals]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[PAK vs BAN match today: Pakistan must win to maintain hopes of semi-finals

Pakistan will face Bangladesh today in the 31st match of ODI World Cup 2023. The match will be played at Eden Garden Stadium, Kolkata from 2:00 pm onwards. The toss will take place at 1:30 p.m.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/PAK-vs BAN match today- Pakistan must win to maintain hopes of semi-finals/802</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/PAK-vs BAN match today- Pakistan must win to maintain hopes of semi-finals/802</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 06:11:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NZ vs SA Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction, NZ vs SA World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[NZ vs SA Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction, NZ vs SA World Cup 2023

New Zealand and South Africa will lock horns against each other in their 32nd game of the ongoing ICC Cricket World Cup 2023 in India. The match is set to take place at Maharashtra Cricket Association Stadium in Pune. This is the third match of this World Cup that will be held in this stadium.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/NZ-vs SA Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction- NZ vs SA World Cup 2023/801</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/NZ-vs SA Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction- NZ vs SA World Cup 2023/801</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 06:11:24 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PAK vs BAN Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction, PAK vs BAN World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[PAK vs BAN Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction, PAK vs BAN World Cup 2023]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/PAK-vs BAN Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction- PAK vs BAN World Cup 2023/800</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/PAK-vs BAN Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction- PAK vs BAN World Cup 2023/800</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 06:26:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AFG Vs SL match today: Afghanistan has a chance to defeat Lanka for the first time in the World Cup.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[AFG Vs SL match today: Afghanistan has a chance to defeat Lanka for the first time in the World Cup.

Sri Lanka will face Afghanistan in the 30th match of the World Cup 2023 today i.e. on 30th October. The match will be played at the Maharashtra Cricket Association (MCA) Stadium in Pune from 2:00 pm onwards. Like every match, the toss in this match too will take place half an hour earlier i.e. at 1:30 pm.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/AFG-Vs SL match today- Afghanistan has a chance to defeat Lanka for the first time in the World Cup-/799</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/AFG-Vs SL match today- Afghanistan has a chance to defeat Lanka for the first time in the World Cup-/799</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2023 06:13:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AFG vs SL Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction, AFG vs SL World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[AFG vs SL Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction, AFG vs SL World Cup 2023

Afghanistan and Sri Lanka will lock horns against each in their 30th game of the ongoing ICC Cricket World Cup 2023 in India. The match is set to take place at Maharashtra Cricket Association Stadium in Pune. This is the second match of this World Cup will be held in this stadium.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/AFG-vs SL Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction- AFG vs SL World Cup 2023/798</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/AFG-vs SL Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction- AFG vs SL World Cup 2023/798</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 06:43:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IND vs ENG: Team India has not been able to beat England in the tournament for 20 years]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[IND vs ENG: Team India has not been able to beat England in the tournament for 20 years.

The teams of India and England will clash for the 9th time in the history of the World Cup. The match will be held at Bharat Ratna Shri Atal Bihari Vajpayee Ekana Cricket Stadium in Lucknow from 2 pm. Team India would like to secure its place in the semi-finals by defeating England today. At the same time, England would like to keep their hopes alive by defeating India in the World Cup.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/IND-vs ENG- Team India has not been able to beat England in the tournament for 20 years/797</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/IND-vs ENG- Team India has not been able to beat England in the tournament for 20 years/797</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 05:49:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IND Vs ENG Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction, IND Vs ENG World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[IND Vs ENG Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction, IND Vs ENG World Cup 2023

In the 29th match of the ODI World Cup 2023, India will go head-to-head against England at the Ekana Cricket Stadium in Lucknow. This match is going to be very important specially for England. Because England has won only one match and lost four matches so far in this competition. This match will be do or die for them.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/IND-Vs ENG Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction- IND Vs ENG World Cup 2023/796</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/IND-Vs ENG Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction- IND Vs ENG World Cup 2023/796</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 09:12:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Australian team announced for the series against India: Matthew Wade given captaincy]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Australian team announced for the series against India: Matthew Wade given captaincy

Australia team has been announced for the five-match T20 series to be played against India. Cricket Australia has selected 14 players for the series to be played after the World Cup on Saturday. The captaincy of the team has been handed over to Matthew Wade.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Australian-team announced for the series against India- Matthew Wade given captaincy/795</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Australian-team announced for the series against India- Matthew Wade given captaincy/795</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 08:40:58 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AUS vs NZ Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction, AUS vs NZ World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[AUS vs NZ Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction, AUS vs NZ World Cup 2023]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/AUS-vs NZ Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction- AUS vs NZ World Cup 2023/793</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/AUS-vs NZ Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction- AUS vs NZ World Cup 2023/793</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 05:15:21 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SA vs PAK: Victory is necessary for Pakistan to remain in the semi-finals]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[SA vs PAK: Victory is necessary for Pakistan to remain in the semi-finals.

The 26th match of ODI World Cup 2023 will be played today between South Africa and Pakistan. The match will start at 2:00 pm at Chepauk ground in Chennai, the toss of which will be done at 1:30 pm.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/SA-vs PAK- Victory is necessary for Pakistan to remain in the semi-finals/792</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/SA-vs PAK- Victory is necessary for Pakistan to remain in the semi-finals/792</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 04:54:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ENG vs SL: England has not been able to beat Sri Lanka in the tournament for 16 years]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[ENG vs SL: England has not been able to beat Sri Lanka in the tournament for 16 years

The defending champion England team will face Sri Lanka in the ODI World Cup 2023 today on 26th October. The match will be played at M Chinnaswamy Stadium in Bengaluru from 2 pm onwards. The toss will take place half an hour earlier at 1:30 pm.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ENG-vs SL- England has not been able to beat Sri Lanka in the tournament for 16 years/791</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ENG-vs SL- England has not been able to beat Sri Lanka in the tournament for 16 years/791</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 05:31:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PAK vs SA Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction, PAK vs SA World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[PAK vs SA Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction, PAK vs SA World Cup 2023

Pakistan and South Africa will lock horns in the 26th match of the ongoing World Cup in India. The clash is scheduled to take place at the MA Chidambaram Stadium in Chennai. This is South Africa&rsquo;s first match of this World Cup at this venue while Pakistan lost their game against Afghanistan here earlier this week.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/PAK-vs SA Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction- PAK vs SA World Cup 2023/790</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/PAK-vs SA Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction- PAK vs SA World Cup 2023/790</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 05:29:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Australia's biggest win in ODI World Cup history: Maxwell's fastest century]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Australia&#39;s biggest win in ODI World Cup history: Maxwell&#39;s fastest century

Wednesday was a record-breaking day in the World Cup. Many records were broken on this day. Australia defeated Netherlands by 309 runs at Delhi ground. This was the biggest win in World Cup history in terms of runs. Glenn Maxwell scored the fastest century of the World Cup. Also, David Warner scored his sixth century in the World Cup. You will read some such records further in this story.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Australia-s-biggest win in ODI World Cup history- Maxwell-s fastest century/789</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Australia-s-biggest win in ODI World Cup history- Maxwell-s fastest century/789</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 05:10:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ENG vs SL Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction, ENG vs SL World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[ENG vs SL Dream11 Prediction, Today Match Prediction, ENG vs SL World Cup 2023

The match no. 25 of the tournament will have England (ENG) and Sri Lanka (SL) going head-to-head at M Chinnaswamy Stadium in Bengaluru on Thursday, 26th October. This day-night fixture is scheduled to kick off at 2:00 PM IST.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ENG-vs SL Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction- ENG vs SL World Cup 2023/788</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ENG-vs SL Dream11 Prediction- Today Match Prediction- ENG vs SL World Cup 2023/788</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 05:33:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AUS vs NED: Both teams will face each other for the third time in ODI]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[AUS vs NED: Both teams will face each other for the third time in ODI

In the ODI World Cup 2023, the match will be played between Australia and Netherlands today on 25th October. The match will be played at Arun Jaitley Stadium in Delhi from 2 pm. The toss will take place half an hour earlier at 1:30 pm.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/AUS-vs NED- Both teams will face each other for the third time in ODI/787</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/AUS-vs NED- Both teams will face each other for the third time in ODI/787</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 05:24:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SA vs BAN: 4 matches took place in tournament history, both won 2-2]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[SA vs BAN: 4 matches took place in tournament history, both won 2-2

South Africa will face Bangladesh in the ODI World Cup 2023 today i.e. on Monday 24th October. The match will start at 2 pm at Wankhede Stadium, Mumbai. The toss will take place half an hour before the start of the match i.e. at 1:30 pm.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/SA-vs BAN- 4 matches took place in tournament history- both won 2-2/786</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/SA-vs BAN- 4 matches took place in tournament history- both won 2-2/786</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 03:45:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Afghanistan defeated Pakistan for the first time in ODI]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Afghanistan defeated Pakistan for the first time in ODI: Third upset of World Cup 2023, chased the target of 283 in 49 overs.

The pair of captain Shahidi and Rahmat Shah made an unbeaten partnership of 96 runs and led the team to victory.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Afghanistan-defeated Pakistan for the first time in ODI/785</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Afghanistan-defeated Pakistan for the first time in ODI/785</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 03:28:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Australia vs Netherlands Dream11 prediction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[&nbsp;Australia vs Netherlands Dream11 prediction]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Australia-vs Netherlands Dream11 prediction/784</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Australia-vs Netherlands Dream11 prediction/784</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 08:36:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[South Africa Vs Bangladesh Dream11 prediction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[South Africa Vs Bangladesh Dream11 prediction 

South Africa (SA) will lock horns against the Bangladesh (BAN) on Tuesday (Oct 24) at the Wankhede Stadium, Mumbai in the 23rd game of the WC 2023. South Africa is at third position in the points table after winning three out of four matches.&nbsp; Whereas Bangladesh has won only one match out of four and is at sixth position in the points table.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/South-Africa Vs Bangladesh Dream11 prediction/783</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/South-Africa Vs Bangladesh Dream11 prediction/783</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 07:53:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[England Vs South Africa Dream11 prediction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[England Vs South Africa Dream11 prediction&nbsp;&nbsp;ENG vs SA Dream11 prediction, ENG vs SA&nbsp; Playing 11]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/England-Vs South Africa Dream11 prediction/782</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/England-Vs South Africa Dream11 prediction/782</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 06:40:06 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[India Vs New Zealand Dream11 prediction, IND vs NZ Dream11 prediction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[India Vs New Zealand Dream11 prediction, IND vs NZ Dream11 prediction, IND vs NZ

In the 21st match of the ODI World Cup, India will be locking horns against the New Zealand at the Himachal Pradesh Cricket Association Stadium in Dharamsala. This match is between the top two teams of the tournament. Both the teams have won all their matches. Where India defeated Bangladesh by 7 wickets in the last match. Whereas New Zealand had defeated Afghanistan by 149 runs.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-Vs New Zealand Dream11 prediction- IND vs NZ Dream11 prediction/781</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-Vs New Zealand Dream11 prediction- IND vs NZ Dream11 prediction/781</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 06:39:46 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Australia vs Pakistan Fantasy-11 and Dream11 prediction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Australia vs Pakistan Fantasy-11 and Dream11 prediction, AUS VS PAK&nbsp;Dream11 prediction, AUS VS PAK&nbsp; Playing 11

Today in the ODI World Cup, the World Cup group match will be played between Australia and Pakistan. The match will be held at Chinnaswamy Stadium in Bengaluru from 2 pm.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Australia-vs Pakistan Fantasy-11 and Dream11 prediction/780</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Australia-vs Pakistan Fantasy-11 and Dream11 prediction/780</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 20 Oct 2023 05:00:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[World Cup 2023: IND vs BAN; India has a chance for a fourth victory]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[World Cup 2023: IND vs BAN; India has a chance for a fourth victory

India will face Bangladesh in the ODI World Cup 2023 today, on Thursday, 19 October. The match will be played at Maharashtra Cricket Association Stadium, Pune from 2 pm. The toss will take place half an hour earlier at 1:30 pm. By winning today&#39;s match, Team India can win its fourth consecutive match, the team also has a chance to surpass New Zealand and come on top in the points table.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/World-Cup 2023- IND vs BAN- India has a chance for a fourth victory/779</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/World-Cup 2023- IND vs BAN- India has a chance for a fourth victory/779</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 05:47:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[India Vs Bangladesh Dream11 prediction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[India Vs Bangladesh Dream11 prediction, Today Match Prediction, IND vs BNG, World Cup 2023]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-Vs Bangladesh Dream11 prediction/778</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-Vs Bangladesh Dream11 prediction/778</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 05:06:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Zealand vs Afghanistan]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[New Zealand won all three of its matches, and Afghanistan morale is high after defeating England in the last match.

In the ODI World Cup 2023, the match will be played between New Zealand and Afghanistan today. on Tuesday 18 October. The match will take place at 2 pm at MA Chidambaram Stadium (Chepauk), Chennai. The toss will take place half an hour earlier at 1:30 pm.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/New-Zealand vs Afghanistan/777</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/New-Zealand vs Afghanistan/777</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 07:14:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Second upset in 3 days in the World Cup: Netherlands beat South Africa by 38 runs]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Second upset in 3 days in the World Cup: Netherlands beat South Africa by 38 runs; All out for 207 runs

Netherlands has defeated South Africa by 38 runs in the World Cup 2023. This is the second major reversal within the last 3 days. Earlier on October 15, Afghanistan had defeated world champion England by 69 runs in Delhi.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Second-upset in 3 days in the World Cup- Netherlands beat South Africa by 38 runs/776</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Second-upset in 3 days in the World Cup- Netherlands beat South Africa by 38 runs/776</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 05:19:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Zealand Vs Afghanistan Dream11 prediction, NZ vs AFG Dream11 prediction, NZ vs AFG Playing 11]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[New Zealand Vs Afghanistan Dream11 prediction, NZ&nbsp;vs AFG Dream11 prediction, NZ&nbsp;vs AFG Playing 11

New Zealand and Afghanistan will lock horns against each other in their 16th game of the ongoing ICC Cricket World Cup 2023 in India. The match is set to take place at the MA Chidambaram Stadium in Chennai, the venue that hosted the India vs Australia encounter on October 8.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/New-Zealand Vs Afghanistan Dream11 prediction- NZ-vs AFG Dream11 prediction- NZ-vs AFG Playing 11/775</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/New-Zealand Vs Afghanistan Dream11 prediction- NZ-vs AFG Dream11 prediction- NZ-vs AFG Playing 11/775</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 06:41:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[South Africa vs Netherlands: South Africa has a chance to become table topper]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[South Africa vs Netherlands: South Africa has a chance to become table topper; Netherlands looking for first win]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/South-Africa vs Netherlands- South Africa has a chance to become table topper/774</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/South-Africa vs Netherlands- South Africa has a chance to become table topper/774</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 06:17:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SA vs NL Dream11 prediction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[South Africa Vs Netherlands Dream11 prediction,&nbsp;SA vs NL Dream11 Playing XI, SA vs NL Playing 11]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/SA-vs NL Dream11 prediction/773</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/SA-vs NL Dream11 prediction/773</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 05:37:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Australia vs Sri Lanka: Both teams have a chance to open the account of victory]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Australia vs Sri Lanka: Both teams have a chance to open the account of victory.

Today in the ODI World Cup 2023, the match will be played between Australia and Sri Lanka. The match will be played at Bharat Ratna Shri Atal Bihari Vajpayee Cricket Stadium (Ikana), Lucknow from 2 pm. The toss will take place half an hour earlier at 1:30 pm.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Australia-vs Sri Lanka- Both teams have a chance to open the account of victory/772</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Australia-vs Sri Lanka- Both teams have a chance to open the account of victory/772</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 05:25:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[First upset of World Cup 2023: Afghanistan defeated defending champion England]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[First upset of World Cup 2023: Afghanistan defeated defending champion England.

Afghanistan caused the biggest upset of the ODI World Cup 2023. The team registered a historic win over defending champions England, defeating them by 69 runs. After losing 14 consecutive matches in the World Cup, Afghanistan registered victory and defeated the 2019 champion team. Earlier the team had defeated Scotland in 2015.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/First-upset of World Cup 2023- Afghanistan defeated defending champion England/771</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/First-upset of World Cup 2023- Afghanistan defeated defending champion England/771</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 05:14:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Australia Vs Sri Lanka Dream11 Prediction, AUS vs SL Dream11 Playing XI, AUS vs SL Playing 11]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[&nbsp;Australia Vs Sri Lanka Dream11 Prediction

In the 14th match of the ODI World Cup 2023, Australia will go head-to-head against Sri Lanka at the Ekana Cricket Stadium in Lucknow. This match is going to be very important for both the teams because both the teams have lost both their starting matches.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Australia-Vs Sri Lanka Dream11 Prediction- AUS vs SL Dream11 Playing XI- AUS vs SL Playing 11/770</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Australia-Vs Sri Lanka Dream11 Prediction- AUS vs SL Dream11 Playing XI- AUS vs SL Playing 11/770</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 02:55:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ENG vs AFG Dream11 Prediction, Dream11 Playing XI, ENG vs AFG Playing 11 | ENG vs AFG]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[ENG vs AFG Dream11 Prediction, Dream11 Playing 

England cricket team will face Afghanistan in the 13th contest of the ICC Cricket World Cup 2023. This high-stakes encounter is scheduled for 15th October 2023 at 2:00 PM (Indian Time) and will take place at the Arun Jaitley Stadium, Delhi.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ENG-vs AFG Dream11 Prediction- Dream11 Playing XI-ENG vs AFG Playing 11 - ENG vs AFG/769</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ENG-vs AFG Dream11 Prediction- Dream11 Playing XI-ENG vs AFG Playing 11 - ENG vs AFG/769</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 02:09:46 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[India defeated Pakistan for the 8th consecutive time in ODI World Cup]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[India defeated Pakistan for the 8th consecutive time in ODI World Cup

The Indian team achieved the target of 192 runs in 30.3 overs. Captain Rohit Sharma played an inning of 86 runs. He made a partnership of 77 runs with Shreyas Iyer for the third wicket. Jasprit Bumrah, who took 2 wickets for 19 runs, was the player of the match.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-defeated Pakistan for the 8th consecutive time in ODI World Cup/768</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-defeated Pakistan for the 8th consecutive time in ODI World Cup/768</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 17:38:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[India vs Pakistan: Head-to-Head Record and Possible Playing-1]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[India vs Pakistan: Head-to-Head Record and Possible Playing-1

The biggest match of the league stage of ODI World Cup 2023, India-Pakistan match will be played today. The match will start at 2:00 pm at Narendra Modi Stadium, Ahmedabad. The toss will take place half an hour earlier at 1:30 pm.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-vs Pakistan- Head-to-Head Record and Possible Playing-1/767</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-vs Pakistan- Head-to-Head Record and Possible Playing-1/767</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2023 03:57:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shaheen said - I will take 5 wickets for India, then I will take a photo.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Shaheen said - I will take 5 wickets for India, then I will take a photo.

Shaheen Afridi told a fan in Ahmedabad that he would get photographed only after taking 5 wickets against India on October 14.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Shaheen-said - I will take 5 wickets for India- then I will take a photo-/766</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Shaheen-said - I will take 5 wickets for India- then I will take a photo-/766</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 12:56:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bollywood Singer- Rock show Will Be Held Before The India-Pak Match | IND vs PAK Dream11 prediction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Bollywood Singer- Rock Show Will Be Held Before The India-Pak Match 

Shankar Mahadev, Arijit Singh, and Sukhwinder Singh will perform before the toss at Narendra Modi Stadium.

There will be a musical event before the World Cup match between India and Pakistan. This was announced by the Board of Control for Cricket in India (BCCI) late on Thursday night through social media X. The World Cup match between India and Pakistan is to be played on October 14 at Narendra Modi Stadium in Ahmedabad. Both the teams have reached Ahmedabad.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Bollywood-Singer- Rock show Will Be Held Before The India-Pak Match - IND vs PAK Dream11 prediction/765</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Bollywood-Singer- Rock show Will Be Held Before The India-Pak Match - IND vs PAK Dream11 prediction/765</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 06:41:06 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[India vs Pakistan World Cup 2023 | India vs Pakistan prediction | Dream11 prediction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[India vs Pakistan World Cup 2023]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-vs Pakistan World Cup 2023 - India vs Pakistan prediction - Dream11 prediction/764</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-vs Pakistan World Cup 2023 - India vs Pakistan prediction - Dream11 prediction/764</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 05:20:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IND VS PAK Dream11 prediction | IND vs PAK Playing 11 | IND vs PAK | IND vs PAK World Cup]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[India vs Pakistan: Dream 11 prediction

India and Pakistan will lock horns against each other in 12th game of ongoing ICC Cricket World Cup 2023 in India. The match is set to take place at the Narendra Modi Stadium in Ahmedabad, the venue which hosted World Cup 2023 opener, England vs New Zealand on October 5.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/IND-VS PAK Dream11 prediction - IND vs PAK Playing 11 - IND vs PAK - IND vs PAK World Cup/763</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/IND-VS PAK Dream11 prediction - IND vs PAK Playing 11 - IND vs PAK - IND vs PAK World Cup/763</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 06:27:49 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AUS vs SA: South Africa has a chance to win 5th consecutive ODI]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[AUS vs SA: South Africa has a chance to win 5th consecutive ODI

Australia will face South Africa in the World Cup 2023 today, on Thursday 12th October. This match will be played at Bharat Ratna Shri Atal Bihari Vajpayee Ekana Stadium, Lucknow from 2 pm. The toss will take place half an hour earlier at 1:30 pm.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/AUS-vs SA- South Africa has a chance to win 5th consecutive ODI/762</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/AUS-vs SA- South Africa has a chance to win 5th consecutive ODI/762</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 05:38:30 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[India won due to Rohit attack and Bumrah bowling: Kohli hit the winning shot in Delhi]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[India won due to Rohit attack and Bumrah bowling: Kohli hit the winning shot in Delhi

India has registered its second consecutive win in the ODI World Cup 2023. After Australia, Team India also registered a one-sided victory over Afghanistan. Afghanistan won the toss and chose to bat at the Arun Jaitley Stadium in New Delhi. The team scored 272 runs for 8 wickets in 50 overs. Jasprit Bumrah took 4 wickets.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-won due to Rohit attack and Bumrah bowling- Kohli hit the winning shot in Delhi/761</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-won due to Rohit attack and Bumrah bowling- Kohli hit the winning shot in Delhi/761</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 04:58:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Zealand vs Bangladesh Dream11 predication]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[New Zealand vs Bangladesh Dream11 predication

New Zealand and Bangladesh will lock horns against each in their third game of the ongoing ICC Cricket World Cup 2023 in India. The match is set to take place at the MA Chidambaram Stadium in Chennai, the venue which hosted the India vs Australia encounter last Sunday (October 8).]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/New-Zealand vs Bangladesh Dream11 predication/760</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/New-Zealand vs Bangladesh Dream11 predication/760</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 07:02:41 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Australia Vs South Africa Dream11 prediction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Australia Vs South Africa Dream11 prediction

In the 10th match of the ODI World Cup 2023, Australia will go head-to-head against South Africa at the Ekana Cricket Stadium in Lucknow. The team from down under had a tough start to their campaign in the flagship tournament against the hosts India, while the Proteas got the better of Sri Lanka. In their recent series in the ODI format, South Africa defeated Australia with a close margin of 3-2, which could mean a banger of a contest on October 12 between these two sides.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Australia-Vs South Africa Dream11 prediction/759</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Australia-Vs South Africa Dream11 prediction/759</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 06:29:13 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[India vs Afghanistan: Ishaan will play in this match in place of Gill; possible playing 11]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[India vs Afghanistan: Ishaan will play in this match in place of Gill; possible playing 11]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-vs Afghanistan- Ishaan will play in this match in place of Gill- possible playing 11/758</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-vs Afghanistan- Ishaan will play in this match in place of Gill- possible playing 11/758</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 05:37:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[India vs Afghanistan Dream11 prediction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[India vs Afghanistan Dream11 prediction

India will take on the challenge of Afghanistan in the 9th match of the ODI World Cup 2023 at the Arun Jaitley Stadium in Delhi. The hosts got the better of the former five-time champions Australia by six wickets in comfortable manner, while their upcoming opponents were badly beaten by Bangladesh with a margin of six wickets too. In their short history, Afghanistan has never managed to defeat India in an ODI, which would put the former two-time champions in the box seat on October 11.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-vs Afghanistan Dream11 prediction/757</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-vs Afghanistan Dream11 prediction/757</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 11:52:55 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ICC World Cup 2023: The Fastest Century Hits By Sri Lanka Batter Kusal Mendis In World Cup History]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[In the history of ODI World Cups, Sri Lanka batsman Kusal Mendis has broken the record held by famous batsman Kumar Sangakkara by scoring the nation&#39;s quickest century. In Hyderabad&#39;s Rajiv Gandhi International Stadium against Pakistan, Mendis scored a century off just 65 balls.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ICC-World Cup 2023- The Fastest Century Hits By Sri Lanka Batter Kusal Mendis In World Cup History/756</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ICC-World Cup 2023- The Fastest Century Hits By Sri Lanka Batter Kusal Mendis In World Cup History/756</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 11:33:13 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shubman Gill admitted to hospital for treatment of dengue]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Shubman Gill admitted to hospital for treatment of dengue

Team India&#39;s opener Shubman Gill has been admitted to the hospital in Chennai. Gill is suffering from dengue. According to media reports, Gill was admitted to Kauvery Hospital on Monday morning. A team of doctors kept an eye on him under the supervision of Dr. Rizwan Khan of the Board of Control for Cricket in India (BCCI).]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Shubman-Gill admitted to hospital for treatment of dengue/755</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Shubman-Gill admitted to hospital for treatment of dengue/755</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 06:01:59 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[England Vs Bangladesh Fantasy-11 and dream11 prediction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[England Vs Bangladesh Fantasy-11 and dream11 prediction

&nbsp;]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/England-Vs Bangladesh Fantasy-11 and dream11 prediction/754</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/England-Vs Bangladesh Fantasy-11 and dream11 prediction/754</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 07:57:08 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sri Lanka vs Pakistan Fantasy-11 and dream11 prediction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Sri Lanka vs Pakistan Fantasy-11 and dream11 prediction

In the 8th match of the ODI World Cup 2023, Pakistan will go head-to-head against Sri Lanka at the Rajiv Gandhi International Stadium in Hyderabad. The Men in Green started their campaign in the flagship tournament with a comprehensive win against Netherlands, while the island nation were demolished by South Africa the other day too. But, in their previous encounter last month, Sri Lanka got the better of Pakistan at the Asia Cup 2023, which will keep them in good stead in their upcoming fixture.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Sri-Lanka vs Pakistan Fantasy-11 and dream11 prediction/753</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Sri-Lanka vs Pakistan Fantasy-11 and dream11 prediction/753</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 07:56:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New Zealand vs Netherlands Fantasy-11 and dream11 prediction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[New Zealand vs Netherlands Fantasy-11 and dream11 prediction]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/New-Zealand vs Netherlands Fantasy-11 and dream11 prediction/752</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/New-Zealand vs Netherlands Fantasy-11 and dream11 prediction/752</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 06:36:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[India's winning start in the World Cup: Australia was defeated by 6 wickets]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[India&#39;s winning start in the World Cup: Australia was defeated by 6 wickets, Rahul won by hitting a six; Kohli scored 85 runs

6 wickets defeated Australia, Rahul won by hitting a six; Kohli scored 85 runs|World Cup]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-s-winning start in the World Cup- Australia was defeated by 6 wickets/751</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-s-winning start in the World Cup- Australia was defeated by 6 wickets/751</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 17:44:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[India vs Australia Fantasy XI And Dream 11 Prediction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[India vs Australia Fantasy XI And Dream 11 Prediction ]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-vs Australia Fantasy XI And Dream 11 Prediction/750</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-vs Australia Fantasy XI And Dream 11 Prediction/750</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 07:44:17 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bangladesh beat Afghanistan by 6 wickets: Miraj's double performance]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Bangladesh beat Afghanistan by 6 wickets: Miraj&#39;s double performance

innings of 57 runs and took three wickets.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Bangladesh-beat Afghanistan by 6 wickets- Miraj-s double performance/749</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Bangladesh-beat Afghanistan by 6 wickets- Miraj-s double performance/749</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 16:53:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bangladesh vs Afghanistan Dream11 Prediction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Bangladesh-vs Afghanistan Dream11 Prediction/748</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Bangladesh-vs Afghanistan Dream11 Prediction/748</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 05:45:41 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[South Africa vs Sri Lanka Dream11 Prediction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[South Africa&#39;s biggest strength heading into the tournament and there are a lot of expectations from Heinrich Klaasen based on his current form

Which team will win today&#39;s World Cup match between SA and SL? Match 4 of the 2023 ICC World Cup. SA versus SL On October 7, a match for the ICC World Cup 2023 will take place in Delhi. At 10.30 IST, the contest will begin. The first of the two games on Saturday and the fourth overall in the campaign is this one. ]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/South-Africa vs Sri Lanka Dream11 Prediction/747</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/South-Africa vs Sri Lanka Dream11 Prediction/747</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 12:32:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Shubman Gill's Health Deteriorated, Dengue Fever Occurred]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Shubman Gill&#39;s Health Deteriorated, Dengue Fever Occurred

Doubt overplaying the first match of the World Cup; Team India will face Australia on October 8]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Shubman-Gill-s Health Deteriorated- Dengue Fever Occurred/746</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Shubman-Gill-s Health Deteriorated- Dengue Fever Occurred/746</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 06:50:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sachin Tendulkar Predicts That India Can Be Winner Of ICC World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The legendary Indian cricketer Sachin Tendulkar has named the four teams he thinks will compete in the semi-finals of the 2023 Cricket World Cup in India.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Sachin-Tendulkar Predicts That India Can Be Winner Of ICC World Cup 2023/745</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Sachin-Tendulkar Predicts That India Can Be Winner Of ICC World Cup 2023/745</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 05:34:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PAK vs NED: Fantasy 11 And Dream 11 Prediction]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[PAK vs NED: Fantasy 11 And Dream 11 Prediction 

PAK vs NED Weather Report and Hyderabad Stadium Pitch Report, ICC World Cup 2023, Match 2

Pakistan vs Netherlands, ICC World Cup 2023

PAK vs NED Weather Report Today Live and Hyderabad Stadium Pitch Report, ICC World Cup 2023, Match 2. Pakistan and Netherlands are set to face each other in their first match of the ICC World Cup 2023. The PAK vs NED match is scheduled to be played on Friday, October 6 at the Rajiv Gandhi International Stadium, Hyderabad.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/PAK-vs NED- Fantasy 11 And Dream 11 Prediction/744</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/PAK-vs NED- Fantasy 11 And Dream 11 Prediction/744</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 05:06:24 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[India-Australia Team Reached Chennai For World Cup]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[India-Australia Team Reached Chennai For World Cup

Kohli-Warner was seen in a cool mood at the airport, both teams will compete on October 8.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-Australia-Team Reached Chennai For World Cup/742</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-Australia-Team Reached Chennai For World Cup/742</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 10:39:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[England vs New Zealand; dream11 prediction of today's match]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[ODI World Cup starts today: England vs New Zealand; dream11 prediction of today&#39;s match

Opening match between 2019 finalists England-New Zealand]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/England-vs New Zealand- dream11 prediction of today-s match/741</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/England-vs New Zealand- dream11 prediction of today-s match/741</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 05:27:36 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fantasy Cricket Pitch Report For Match 10 Of The ICC Men's T20 World Cup For SAU VS QAT]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[On Wednesday, October 4, at the West End Park International Cricket Stadium in Doha, Saudi Arabia (SAU) and Qatar (QAT) will face off in the tenth game of the ICC Men&#39;s T20 World Cup Sub Regional Asia Qualifier A. Here is everything you need to know about the SAU versus QAT Dream11 Prediction, today&#39;s playing 11, fantasy cricket advice, and the pitch report in advance of this thrilling game.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Fantasy-Cricket Pitch Report For Match 10 Of The ICC Men-s T20 World Cup For SAU VS QAT/736</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Fantasy-Cricket Pitch Report For Match 10 Of The ICC Men-s T20 World Cup For SAU VS QAT/736</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 11:17:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ICC Cricket World Cup 2023: Babar-Rohit Met In Ahmedabad]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[ICC Cricket World Cup 2023: Babar-Rohit Met In Ahmedabad&nbsp;]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ICC-Cricket World Cup 2023- Babar-Rohit Met In Ahmedabad/735</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ICC-Cricket World Cup 2023- Babar-Rohit Met In Ahmedabad/735</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 10:49:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ICC Made Sachin The Global Brand Ambassador Of The World Cup]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[ICC Made Sachin The Global Brand Ambassador Of The World Cup

Tendulkar said - World Cup has a special place in my heart.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ICC-Made Sachin The Global Brand Ambassador Of The World Cup/734</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/ICC-Made Sachin The Global Brand Ambassador Of The World Cup/734</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 08:05:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No Opening Ceremony In 2023 ODI World Cup Everything You Should Know]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The ceremony is going to feature many Bollywood stars lineup including Ranveer Singh, Arijit Singh, Tamannaah Bhatia, Shreya Ghoshal, and Asha Bhosle.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/No-Opening Ceremony In 2023 ODI World Cup Everything You Should Know/733</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/No-Opening Ceremony In 2023 ODI World Cup Everything You Should Know/733</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 05:28:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Who Will Become Champion In 2023: India, Pakistan, Australia or England?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[After a long wait, the World Cup is going to be held in India again. 10 different teams will compete in the field for the trophy but there will be only one champion.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Who-Will Become Champion In 2023- India- Pakistan- Australia or England-/731</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Who-Will Become Champion In 2023- India- Pakistan- Australia or England-/731</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 06:41:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Yashasvi Jaiswal breaks Shubman Gill's India record with maiden T20I century against Nepal]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Jaiswal became the country&#39;s first centurion in the multi-sport event and also broke Shubman Gill&#39;s new T20 record

Yashasvi Jaiswal created a stellar record for India as they made a remarkable start to their 2023 Asian Games campaign in Hangzhou, China, where the Ruturaj Gaikwad-led Men in Blue defeated Nepal in the quarterfinal match at the Pingfeng Campus Cricket Field. , India&#39;s young opening batsman became the country&#39;s first centurion in the multi-sport event and also broke Shubman Gill&#39;s new T20 record.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Yashasvi-Jaiswal breaks Shubman Gill-s India record with maiden T20I century against Nepal/730</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Yashasvi-Jaiswal breaks Shubman Gill-s India record with maiden T20I century against Nepal/730</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 06:09:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PAK poor start to WC preparations, lossed to New Zealand by 5 wickets in their first warm-up match]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/PAK-poor start to WC preparations- lossed to New Zealand by 5 wickets in their first warm-up match/728</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/PAK-poor start to WC preparations- lossed to New Zealand by 5 wickets in their first warm-up match/728</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 16:12:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[India-England World Cup warm-up match today]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[India-England World Cup warm-up match today

The series of warm-up matches continues before the ODI World Cup 2023. 2 matches will be played on Saturday. India and England will face each other in Guwahati, while Netherlands will face Australia in Thiruvananthapuram.The match between India and England will start at 2:00 pm. The toss will take place half an hour earlier i.e. at 1:30 pm.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-England-World Cup warm-up match today/727</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-England-World Cup warm-up match today/727</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 02:13:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA["Hope India Continue To Play Good Cricket": Sourav Ganguly before ODI World Cup]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/-Hope-India Continue To Play Good Cricket- Sourav Ganguly before ODI World Cup/726</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/-Hope-India Continue To Play Good Cricket- Sourav Ganguly before ODI World Cup/726</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 07:10:41 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ashwin entry in place of Axar in the World Cup team]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Ashwin entry in place of Axar in the World Cup team

Patel out due to injury; India&#39;s first match against Australia on October 8]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Ashwin-entry in place of Axar in the World Cup team/725</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Ashwin-entry in place of Axar in the World Cup team/725</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 05:49:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[world cup 2023 schedule]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[world cup 2023 schedule

World Cup 2023: Starting with England-New Zealand match on October 5;India-Pak match in World Cup on October 15]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/world-cup 2023 schedule/724</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/world-cup 2023 schedule/724</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 06:37:29 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why was there a delay in Pakistan getting India's visa for the World Cup?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Why-was there a delay in Pakistan getting India-s visa for the World Cup-/718</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Why-was there a delay in Pakistan getting India-s visa for the World Cup-/718</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 10:28:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Indian team is ready for World Cup 2023, Indian team World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Indian team is ready for World Cup 2023

Rohit and Virat have experience of 250+ matches in ODI, Both 10-thousands of India in the World Cup; Our 4 bowlers have taken 100+ wickets]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Indian-team is ready for World Cup 2023- Indian team World Cup 2023/717</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Indian-team is ready for World Cup 2023- Indian team World Cup 2023/717</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 10:14:54 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[India's World Cup jersey launched]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[India&#39;s World Cup jersey launched


Tricolor color applied on shoulders; Rohit-Kohli also seen in &#39;3 Ka Dream&#39; theme song
Team India&#39;s new jersey for the ODI World Cup has been launched. Kit sponsor Adidas has added the colors of the tricolor on the shoulder area of the jersey. The Board of Control for Cricket in India (BCCI) revealed the jersey with the theme song &#39;3 Ka Dream Hai Apna&#39;.

The ODI World Cup will be played in India from October 5.
The International Cricket Council (ICC) also released the official song of the World Cup today i.e. Wednesday at 12 noon.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-s-World Cup jersey launched/708</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/India-s-World Cup jersey launched/708</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 05:12:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Tricolor surprise in India's ICC World Cup 2023 jersey]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Tricolor-surprise in India-s ICC World Cup 2023 jersey/707</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Tricolor-surprise in India-s ICC World Cup 2023 jersey/707</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 04:58:30 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Team India is ready for the World Cup]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Team India is ready for the World Cup

Team India is ready for the Mission ODI World Cup. India has made its intentions clear for the biggest cricket tournament by winning the Asia Cup. In this tournament, the management found answers to those questions which were troubling the team for a long time.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Team-India is ready for the World Cup/700</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Team-India is ready for the World Cup/700</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2023 06:14:18 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Afghanistan team announced for ICC Cricket World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Afghanistan team announced for ICC Cricket World Cup 2023

Afghanistan&#39;s team has been announced for the ODI World Cup to be held in India from October 5. The Afghan board has handed over the command of the team to Hashmatullah Shahidi. The board has made major changes in the team for the World Cup campaign. 4 players who played Asia Cup have been dropped from the team, while 3 new faces have been given place.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Afghanistan-team announced for ICC Cricket World Cup 2023/689</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Afghanistan-team announced for ICC Cricket World Cup 2023/689</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 08:02:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Netherlands World Cup team announced]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Netherlands World Cup team announced: Van der Merwe and Colin Ackerman return

Netherlands had qualified for the World Cup by defeating teams like West Indies, Scotland and Zimbabwe.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Netherlands-World Cup team announced/675</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Netherlands-World Cup team announced/675</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Sep 2023 04:32:49 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[South Africa team announced for ODI World Cup]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[South Africa team announced for ODI World Cup: Temba Bavuma is a captain

Temba Bavuma will captain the South African team for the first time in the World Cup.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/South-Africa team announced for ODI World Cup/674</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/South-Africa team announced for ODI World Cup/674</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 05:11:46 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[BCCI will release 4 lakh tickets for the World Cup]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[BCCI will release 4 lakh tickets for the World Cup: will be able to buy from 8 pm on September 8

Ticket sales for the league matches of the World Cup began on 25 August.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/BCCI-will release 4 lakh tickets for the World Cup/672</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/BCCI-will release 4 lakh tickets for the World Cup/672</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 05:42:30 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kohli ignored by Rohit Sharma pinning hopes on Hardik for World Cup]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[&nbsp;]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Kohli-ignored by Rohit Sharma pinning hopes on Hardik for World Cup/670</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Kohli-ignored by Rohit Sharma pinning hopes on Hardik for World Cup/670</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2023 11:11:18 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Team India announced for ODI World Cup 2023]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Team India announced for ODI World Cup 2023

Team India has been announced for the ODI World Cup. BCCI Chief Selector Ajit Agarkar announced the names of 15 players of the team at 1:30 pm Indian time. Team captain Rohit Sharma was also present along with Ajit Agarkar in the press conference held in Kandy, Sri Lanka.]]></description>
            <link>https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Team-India announced for ODI World Cup 2023/667</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">https://g11prediction.com/icc-cricket-world-cup-2023/Team-India announced for ODI World Cup 2023/667</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 10:23:01 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>